bluefx.net 2014-06-26

# BlueFx Privacy Policy

### Your Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used by BlueFx.net. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on all pages.

### Collection of Personal Information

When visiting BlueFx.net, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

All information sent to our email addresses or using our online contact form are only used for business purposes between us two parties. Your information will never be shared or passed on to any third party without your prior consent.

### Links to third party Websites

We sometimes share links and quotes of other websites for your use and reference. We are not in any way responsible for the content and terms of these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own and that it is your responsibility to review their policies.

### Transactions

Limited information is supplied to BlueFx.net in the event of a sale. This includes your name and email address. This information is not sold or distributed to third parties. Credit card payments are processed through our payment provider FastSpring.com. Information is collected solely to securely process the order, and is not accessible to BlueFx.net.

### Changes to this Privacy Statement

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion and without notice.  
If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of BlueFx.net, you may contact at: <http://bluefx.net/contact/>
